<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The easy way to write, deploy and use a serverless API on genezio</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in The easy way to write, deploy and use a serverless API on genezio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rest vs RPC</title><link>/blog/rest-vs-rpc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/rest-vs-rpc/</guid><description>Summary REST and RPC are two distinct approaches to web services and distributed computing. REST is focused on resource manipulation and provides a uniform interface for accessing and modifying resources, while RPC is focused on method invocation and provides a way for applications to access remote services and resources. REST is well-suited for web services that require flexibility and scalability, as it provides a uniform stateless interface for accessing and modifying resources.</description></item><item><title>When to use AWS Lambda and genezio?</title><link>/blog/when-to-use-aws-lambda-and-genezio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/when-to-use-aws-lambda-and-genezio/</guid><description>In recent years, serverless computing has become increasingly popular among developers seeking to simplify the deployment and management of their applications.
AWS Lambda is a well known serverless computing service provided by Amazon Web Services. It allows developers to write functions which are executed in lightweight virtual machines (micro vms) in response to specific events. These virtual machines process requests before returning to a dormant state, with users only paying for the time they are active.</description></item><item><title>Create your first Web3 app</title><link>/blog/create-your-first-web3-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-your-first-web3-app/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to create your first Web3 application on Ethereum using Blast API and genezio. You don’t have to know anything beforehand to follow along. I will introduce you to the most basic blockchain concepts and tools to get you from zero to hero in Web3 development. Excited? Let’s get started 🤩
After following through with this tutorial, you’ll be able to brag to your friends about how you can:</description></item><item><title>Create your first app using ChatGPT</title><link>/blog/create-your-first-app-using-chatgpt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-your-first-app-using-chatgpt/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I will show you how to create an app called the Rephrasing App. The app that you are going to build has a simple UI written in React, uses the ChatGPT API and is deployed on genezio.
It will have two main components: the frontend which will consist of a simple chat-like interface, and the backend which exposes a function meant to rephrase your input text. Once implemented, the Rephrasing App can be used to rephrase text, write better articles or even upgrade your CV.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with genezio</title><link>/blog/getting-started-with-genezio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/getting-started-with-genezio/</guid><description>Introduction genezio is a serverless solution for seamlessly building full-stack web and mobile applications in a scalable and cost-efficient way.
Documentation Only a small part of genezio’s functionality is discussed in this article.
For a complete developer documentation, please go to the official genezio Documentation.
Support If you can’t find the answer to some of your questions in this article or in our documentation, we invite you to join our Discord Community.</description></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>/doc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/doc/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>/docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>End-User License Agreement</title><link>/eula/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/eula/</guid><description>End-User License Agreement (&amp;ldquo;Agreement&amp;rdquo;)
Last updated: January 10th, 2022
Please read this End-User License Agreement carefully before signing into, downloading or using genezio.
Interpretation and Definitions Interpretation The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
Definitions For the purposes of this End-User License Agreement:</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy (“Policy”). This Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide (“Personal Information”) on the https://genez.io/ website (“Website” or “Service”) and any of its related products and services (collectively, “Services”), and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that Personal Information. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update it.</description></item></channel></rss>