<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The easiest way to write, deploy and use a serverless API on genezio</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in The easiest way to write, deploy and use a serverless API on genezio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to add a MongoDB to your genezio project</title><link>/blog/how-to-add-a-mongodb-to-your-genezio-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/how-to-add-a-mongodb-to-your-genezio-project/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I will show you the steps of integrating a Mongo database into your genezio Getting Started project.
Following this tutorial, you will be able to:
Create a free-tier MongoDB Atlas cluster Connect to the MongoDB cluster using a MongoDB client Integrate the Mongo database into your project using mongoose Any time you get stuck or have questions, please contact me on Discord or write me an email at radu@genez.</description></item><item><title>The Evolution of APIs: A History of REST and RPC</title><link>/blog/the-evolution-of-apis-a-history-of-rest-and-rpc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/the-evolution-of-apis-a-history-of-rest-and-rpc/</guid><description>Comparison This article has two main components: the history of the paradigms, and a tutorial on how to implement both paradigms using genezio.
Prerequisites for the tutorial:
Install npm Have an IDE or text editor installed, e.g. Visual Studio Code Create a free genezio account Summary REST and RPC are two distinct approaches to web services and distributed computing. REST is focused on resource manipulation and provides a uniform interface for accessing and modifying resources, while RPC is focused on method invocation and provides a way for applications to access remote services and resources.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking the potential of prompt engineering with genezio</title><link>/blog/unlocking-the-potential-of-prompt-engineering-with-genezio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/unlocking-the-potential-of-prompt-engineering-with-genezio/</guid><description>This is a tutorial on how to build a movie recommendation system using the OpenAI API gpt.3-5-turbo based on the user input.
We are developing an application that generates a list of movies with summarized reviews. We aim to provide a seamless user experience by allowing the user to input their preferences and receive movie suggestions.
A complete demo app can be accessed at https://movie-guru.app.genez.io.
Introduction Welcome to this hands-on tutorial about creating advanced prompts and integrating OpenAI in your project using the OpenAI SDK.</description></item><item><title>Genezio New Release</title><link>/blog/genezio-new-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/genezio-new-release/</guid><description>I’m excited to work with such a productive team! Since our last release, we’ve added some new features, improved a couple of things and resolved a few bugs. Let’s dive in the latest developments made by our amazing team:
Updates We are thrilled to announce that we are officially open source! Enjoy genezio at its fullest by choosing whether to deploy on your own AWS or on genezio. This allows you to have the freedom and flexibility while also making use of our amazing features.</description></item><item><title>The easy way to write, deploy and use a serverless API</title><link>/full-stack-dart-application/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 05:10:04 +0300</pubDate><guid>/full-stack-dart-application/</guid><description>full-stack-dart-application</description></item><item><title>Exploring the Differences Between genezio and Express.js</title><link>/blog/exploring-the-differences-between-genezio-and-express.js/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/exploring-the-differences-between-genezio-and-express.js/</guid><description>APIs are one of the most important tools in software technology and are used for building modern and reliable software products. There are many ways of developing and exposing an API. Over time, frameworks were built, and doing this became much easier and user-friendlier. Today we will compare genezio with one of the major players in the market, Express. Let’s get started!
Express is one of the most popular frameworks used for backend programming.</description></item><item><title>When to use AWS Lambda and genezio?</title><link>/blog/when-to-use-aws-lambda-and-genezio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/when-to-use-aws-lambda-and-genezio/</guid><description>In recent years, serverless computing has become increasingly popular among developers seeking to simplify the deployment and management of their applications.
AWS Lambda is a well known serverless computing service provided by Amazon Web Services. It allows developers to write functions which are executed in lightweight virtual machines (micro vms) in response to specific events. These virtual machines process requests before returning to a dormant state, with users only paying for the time they are active.</description></item><item><title>Create your first Web3 app</title><link>/blog/create-your-first-web3-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-your-first-web3-app/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to create your first Web3 application on Ethereum using Blast API and genezio. You don’t have to know anything beforehand to follow along. I will introduce you to the most basic blockchain concepts and tools to get you from zero to hero in Web3 development. Excited? Let’s get started 🤩
After following through with this tutorial, you’ll be able to brag to your friends about how you can:</description></item><item><title>Create your first app using ChatGPT</title><link>/blog/create-your-first-app-using-chatgpt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-your-first-app-using-chatgpt/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I will show you how to create an app called the Rephrasing App. The app that you are going to build has a simple UI written in React, uses the ChatGPT API and is deployed on genezio.
It will have two main components: the frontend which will consist of a simple chat-like interface, and the backend which exposes a function meant to rephrase your input text. Once implemented, the Rephrasing App can be used to rephrase text, write better articles or even upgrade your CV.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with genezio</title><link>/blog/getting-started-with-genezio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/getting-started-with-genezio/</guid><description>Introduction Genezio is a serverless solution for seamlessly building full-stack web and mobile applications in a scalable and cost-efficient way.
Documentation Only a small part of genezio’s functionality is discussed in this article.
For complete developer documentation, please go to our Official Documentation.
Support We invite you to join our community on Discord for further information and help.
Let’s Get Started This guide will get you up and running with genezio in less than five minutes.</description></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>/doc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/doc/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>/docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>End-User License Agreement</title><link>/eula/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/eula/</guid><description>End-User License Agreement (&amp;ldquo;Agreement&amp;rdquo;)
Last updated: January 10th, 2022
Please read this End-User License Agreement carefully before signing into, downloading or using genezio.
Interpretation and Definitions Interpretation The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
Definitions For the purposes of this End-User License Agreement:</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy (“Policy”). This Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide (“Personal Information”) on the https://genez.io/ website (“Website” or “Service”) and any of its related products and services (collectively, “Services”), and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that Personal Information. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update it.</description></item></channel></rss>