<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Comparison on genezio</title><link>/tags/comparison/</link><description>Recent content in Comparison on genezio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/comparison/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring the Differences Between genezio and Express.js</title><link>/blog/exploring-the-differences-between-genezio-and-express.js/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/exploring-the-differences-between-genezio-and-express.js/</guid><description>APIs are one of the most important tools in software technology and are used for building modern and reliable software products. There are many ways of developing and exposing an API. Over time, frameworks were built, and doing this became much easier and user-friendlier. Today we will compare genezio with one of the major players in the market, Express. Let’s get started!
Express is one of the most popular frameworks used for backend programming.</description></item><item><title>When to use AWS Lambda and genezio?</title><link>/blog/when-to-use-aws-lambda-and-genezio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/when-to-use-aws-lambda-and-genezio/</guid><description>In recent years, serverless computing has become increasingly popular among developers seeking to simplify the deployment and management of their applications.
AWS Lambda is a well known serverless computing service provided by Amazon Web Services. It allows developers to write functions which are executed in lightweight virtual machines (micro vms) in response to specific events. These virtual machines process requests before returning to a dormant state, with users only paying for the time they are active.</description></item></channel></rss>