<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorials on genezio</title><link>/tags/tutorials/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on genezio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unlocking the potential of prompt engineering with genezio</title><link>/blog/unlocking-the-potential-of-prompt-engineering-with-genezio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/unlocking-the-potential-of-prompt-engineering-with-genezio/</guid><description>This is a tutorial on how to build a movie recommendation system using the OpenAI API gpt.3-5-turbo based on the user input.
We are developing an application that generates a list of movies with summarized reviews. We aim to provide a seamless user experience by allowing the user to input their preferences and receive movie suggestions.
A complete demo app can be accessed at https://movie-guru.app.genez.io.
Introduction Welcome to this hands-on tutorial about creating advanced prompts and integrating OpenAI in your project using the OpenAI SDK.</description></item><item><title>Create your first Web3 app</title><link>/blog/create-your-first-web3-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-your-first-web3-app/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to create your first Web3 application on Ethereum using Blast API and genezio. You don’t have to know anything beforehand to follow along. I will introduce you to the most basic blockchain concepts and tools to get you from zero to hero in Web3 development. Excited? Let’s get started 🤩
After following through with this tutorial, you’ll be able to brag to your friends about how you can:</description></item><item><title>Create your first app using ChatGPT</title><link>/blog/create-your-first-app-using-chatgpt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-your-first-app-using-chatgpt/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I will show you how to create an app called the Rephrasing App. The app that you are going to build has a simple UI written in React, uses the ChatGPT API and is deployed on genezio.
It will have two main components: the frontend which will consist of a simple chat-like interface, and the backend which exposes a function meant to rephrase your input text. Once implemented, the Rephrasing App can be used to rephrase text, write better articles or even upgrade your CV.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with genezio</title><link>/blog/getting-started-with-genezio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/getting-started-with-genezio/</guid><description>Introduction Genezio is a serverless solution for seamlessly building full-stack web and mobile applications in a scalable and cost-efficient way.
Documentation Only a small part of genezio’s functionality is discussed in this article.
For complete developer documentation, please go to our Official Documentation.
Support We invite you to join our community on Discord for further information and help.
Let’s Get Started This guide will get you up and running with genezio in less than five minutes.</description></item></channel></rss>