<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on genezio</title><link>/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on genezio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>When to use AWS Lambda and genezio?</title><link>/blog/when-to-use-aws-lambda-and-genezio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/when-to-use-aws-lambda-and-genezio/</guid><description>In recent years, serverless computing has become increasingly popular among developers seeking to simplify the deployment and management of their applications.
AWS Lambda is a well known serverless computing service provided by Amazon Web Services. It allows developers to write functions which are executed in lightweight virtual machines (micro vms) in response to specific events. These virtual machines process requests before returning to a dormant state, with users only paying for the time they are active.</description></item><item><title>Create your first Web3 app</title><link>/blog/create-your-first-web3-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-your-first-web3-app/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to create your first Web3 application on Ethereum using Blast API and genezio. You don’t have to know anything beforehand to follow along. I will introduce you to the most basic blockchain concepts and tools to get you from zero to hero in Web3 development. Excited? Let’s get started 🤩
After following through with this tutorial, you’ll be able to brag to your friends about how you can:</description></item><item><title>Create your first app using ChatGPT</title><link>/blog/create-your-first-app-using-chatgpt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-your-first-app-using-chatgpt/</guid><description>In this tutorial, I will show you how to create an app called the Rephrasing App. The app that you are going to build has a simple UI written in React, uses the ChatGPT API and is deployed on genezio.
It will have two main components: the frontend which will consist of a simple chat-like interface, and the backend which exposes a function meant to rephrase your input text. Once implemented, the Rephrasing App can be used to rephrase text, write better articles or even upgrade your CV.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with genezio</title><link>/blog/getting-started-with-genezio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/getting-started-with-genezio/</guid><description>Introduction genezio is a serverless solution for seamlessly building full-stack web and mobile applications in a scalable and cost-efficient way.
Documentation Only a small part of genezio’s functionality is discussed in this article.
For a complete developer documentation, please go to the official genezio Documentation.
Support If you can’t find the answer to some of your questions in this article or in our documentation, we invite you to join our Discord Community.</description></item></channel></rss>